And coming back to, let's say, "ho", I also want to try creating a document, right?
So I click on it to see what we have, and yep, write it for me, create an outline, start
with a draft, write a blog on a random topic, right?
So I click on write it for me, please write my document for me, absolutely, could it tell
me a bit more about your document?
Yes.
I say it again this time, I tell it to, so this is a whole different tool, right?
The previous one was the chat, so we were chatting with it, but now we are on the create
document tool, right?
So now we're having a pretty simple text editor at the left, and at the right we have
the AI that is waiting for our command to do whatever that we want in the left side, right?